HAKAN GIRGIN

► +41 76 506 9890 | Makan.girgin@epfl.ch | 🗹 hgirgin.github.io Rue de l'ancien-stand 8, Montreux, Switzerland

PROFILE

I am currently Ph.D. candidate in robotics at Ecole Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne (EPFL) and Idiap Research Institute supervised by Dr. Sylvain Calinon. My research focuses on optimization and active iterative refinement of feedback and feedforward control policies for acquiring robust and anticipatory robot skills from demonstration.

EDUCATION

Ph.D. Robotics	2018 – 2023
Ecole Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne (EPFL)	Lausanne, Switzerland
Bachelor of Science Mechanical Engineering	2012 – 2017
Bogazici University, Entrance rank: 0.13%, GPA: 3.90/4.0	Istanbul, Turkey
Exchange semester Mechanical Engineering	2014 – 2015
Ecole Centrale Paris	Paris, France
Francophone Highschool	2007 – 2012
Lycée de Galatasaray, Entrance rank: 0.06% GPA: 85.84/100	Istanbul, Turkey
WORK EXPERIENCE	
Ph.D. Research Assistant	2018 - 2023
Idiap Research Institute, Robot Learning and Interaction Group	Martigny, Switzerland
 Ph.D. research supervised by Dr. Sylvain Calinon 	
 Worked on EU-Horizon2020 project CoLLaboratE 	
Teaching Assistant	2020-2022
Robotics Course, AI-Master Programme, Unidistance	Martigny, Switzerland
 Preparation of exercises in Jupyter notebooks with ROS and in html formats 	
Bachelor Research Assistant	2017 – 2018
Bogazici University Cognitive Robotics and Learning Systems Lab (CoLoRs)	Istanbul, Turkey
Assistance to Dr. Emre Ugur in forming CoLoRs lab	
 Worked on EU-Horizon 2020 project, IMAGINE 	
Product Definition Engineering Intern	2015 – 2016
General Electric Aviation	Istanbul, Turkey
System Engineering Intern	2016
ALTINAY Aerospace & Advanced Technologies	Istanbul, Turkey
Skills	
Languages: Turkich (Nativa) English (Proficient) Evench (Proficient) Language (P1) II	talian (A1) Corman (A1)

Languages: Turkish (Native), English (Proficient), French (Proficient), Japanese (B1), Italian (A1), German (A1)

Programming: Python, Jupyter, MATLAB, Tensorflow, PyTorch, Pyscript

Software: ROS, PyBullet, KDL

PUBLICATIONS

Reactive Anticipatory Robot Skills with Memory	
H. Girgin, J. Jankowski, S. Calinon, International Symposium on Robotics Research	ISRR 2022
Optimization of robot configurations for motion planning in industrial riveting H. Girgin, T. Lembono, R. Cirligeanu, S. Calinon, In Proc. IEEE Intl Conf. on Advanced Robotics	ICAR 2021
Active Learning of Bayesian Probabilistic Movement Primitives T. Kulak, H. Girgin, JM. Odobez, S. Calinon, IEEE Robotics and Automation Letters	RAL 2021
Probabilistic Adaptive Control for Robust Behavior Imitation J. Jankowski, H. Girgin, S. Calinon, IEEE Robotics and Automation Letters	RAL 2021
Active Improvement of Control Policies with Bayesian Gaussian Mixture Model H. Girgin, E. Pignat, N. Jaquier, S. Calinon, IEEE Intl. Conf. on Intelligent Robots and Systems	IROS 2020
Generative Adversarial Training of Product of Policies for Robust and Adaptive Movement Primitives E. Pignat, H. Girgin, S. Calinon, In Proc. Conference on Robot Learning CoRL 2020	
Compliant Parametric Dynamic Movement Primitives E. Ugur, H. Girgin, Robotica, 38(3), pp. 457-474	Robotica 2020
Associative Skill Memory Models H. Girgin, E. Ugur, IEEE Intl. Conf. on Intelligent Robots and Systems	IROS 2018